<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Mitchell Bosley</title>
    <link>http://mbosley.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Mitchell Bosley</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Mitchell Bosley</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 05 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://mbosley.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Hello World</title>
      <link>http://mbosley.github.io/posts/test/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://mbosley.github.io/posts/test/</guid>
      <description>Header Here is a post!
Here is a code block
1print(&amp;#34;Hello World&amp;#34;) Subheader </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Research</title>
      <link>http://mbosley.github.io/research/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://mbosley.github.io/research/</guid>
      <description>Active Projects When Norms Are Not Enough: Using Large Language Models to Distinguish Between Norm-Codifying and Norm-Disrupting Rule Change in Legislatures Description: Dissertation research.
activeText Description: An R package for active learning for text classification.
Publications:
Improving Probabilistic Models in Text Classification via Active Learning Revise &amp;amp; Resubmit at American Political Science Review (APSR), 2023. GitHub Repo
PolLLM Description: A suite of pre-trained large language models for political science.
Legislative Records from Colonial India, 1919-1947 Description: A new dataset of legislative records from colonial India, 1919-1947.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Teaching</title>
      <link>http://mbosley.github.io/teaching/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://mbosley.github.io/teaching/</guid>
      <description>Prepared Courses Foundations of Large Language Models Description: This graduate-level course provides a solid foundation in the theory and practice of large language models, such as GPT-4. Students will learn about the architecture, training methodologies, and applications of these models for social science research, as well as their ethical implications and future research directions.
Keywords: large language models, GPT-4, machine learning, NLP, AI
Syllabus
Introduction to Political Analysis Description: This first-year course provides students with a comprehensive understanding of political analysis, including the study of political systems, ideologies, institutions, and behaviors.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
